

NUMAIR TAHIR UI/UX DESIGNER

+923090724876 numair.ux@gmail.com https://toxinonumair.github.io/numairux/ in /numairux

UI/UX designer with a keen eye for detail.

I have 2 years of experience in graphic design, user experience writing, wireframing, and most importantly, UI and Visual design. I would like to work in a positive environment that values my abilities and provides opportunities for advancement.

Throughout, my main goal has been to produce,

- Data-driven user interface designs
- Adaptable design systems for independent and web-based applications
- UI design that is responsive and multi-screen

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX DESIGNER

Military College of Signals, NUST | Sep 2022 - Mar 2023

UI DESIGNER

EZILINE | MAY 2021 - OCT 2021

HEAD GRAPHIC DESIGNER

NICON Group of Colleges | Jul 2020 - Nov 2020

NOTABLE WORK

HAUNTY APPLICATION

PRO LEAF APPLICATION

OR ATTENDANCE APPLICATION

MUDARIS APPLICATION (PLAYSTORE)

SPOTIFY APPLICATION (CLONE)

TINDER APPLICATION (CLONE)

HUSH APPLICATION (CLONE)

KEY SKILLS

UX RESEARCH

INFORMATION ARCHITECTURE

WIRE-FRAMING

UI DESIGN

VISUAL DESIGN

PROTOTYPING

USABILITY TESTING

EMPATHY

EDUCATION

Riphah International University

2018 - 2022

BS (Software Engineering)

- Graphics Designing
- Human Computer Interaction
- HTML & CSS

SOFTWARES

FIGMA

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

BLENDER